Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 2-627, OV 868)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Music
    - Ferrari, Louis and Don Raye
      - Domino. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1950. (Box-folder 434/3)
    - Fillmore, Henry
      - Lassus trombone. New York: Carl Fischer Inc., 1918. (Box-folder 434/3, 507/3)
    - Fisher, Dave
      - Michael. New York: United Artists Music Co., Inc., 1960. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Fisher, Fred
      - Chicago. New York: Fred Fisher Inc., 1922. (Box-folder 434/3)
      - Peg o' my heart. New York: Robbins Music Co., 1913. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Fisher, Fred and Alfred Bryan
      - Come, Josephine, in my flying machine. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1937., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/3)
    - Fisher, Fred and Thomas L. Gray
      - Any little girl, that's a nice little girl (is the right little girl for me). New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1910. (Box-folder 434/3)
    - Fisher, Fred and McCarthy
      - They go wild over me. McCarthy and Fisher, Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Fisher, Marvin and Kenward Elmsie
      - Love-wise. New York: Marvin Music Co., 1959. (Box-folder 434/3)
    - Fisher, Mark, Joe Goodwin and Larry Shay
      - When your smiling (the whole world smiles with you). (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Fisher, Marvin and Jack Segal
      - (Love is a) Necessary evil. New York: Marvin Music Co. (Box-folder 434/3)
    - Fitch, Art, Kay Fitch and Bert Lowe
      - (I love you - I love you - I love you) Sweetheart of all my dreams. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1953 and 1955. (Box-folder 434/3)
    - Fitzgerald, E.J.
      - Irish washerwoman. Natinal Assoc. of Broadcasters, Inc., 1937. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Fitzgerald, Ella and Van Alexander
      - A-tisket a-tasket. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1938. (Box-folder 434/32)
    - Foley
      - Chicken reel. Boston: Walter Jacobs, Inc., 1910. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Foley, Red
      - John Henry. (Box-folder 507/3)
      - Just a closer walk with tree. New York: Home Folks Music, Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 434/3)
    - Foster, Frank B. and Ella Fitzgerald
      - Shiny stockings. Beverly Hills: Lynnstorm Pub. Co., 1956, 1963 and 1965. (Box-folder 434/3)
    - Foster, Stephen C.
      - Camptown races. Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1936. (Box-folder 507/3)
      - Old folks at home. Bryn Mawr: Oliver Dison Co., 1906. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Freed, Arthur, Gus Arnheim and Abe Lyman
      - I cried for you. New York: Miller Music Corp., 1923. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Freed, Arthur and Roger Edens
      - Our love affair. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Freedman, Max C. and Jimmy DeKnight
      - Rock around the clock. Philadelphia: Myers Music, 1953. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Freire, R. and Solano Y Cabello
      - Doce Cascabeles. Madrid: Union Musical Espanola, 1953. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - French, Percy and Houston Collisson
      - The mountains o'Mourne. New York: Sam Fox Pub. Co., 1937., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/4)
    - French, W.P.
      - Phil the fluter's ball. New York: Sam Fox Pub. Co., 1938., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Frey, Hugo, edited by
      - Merrily we sing: a community song book. New York: Leo Feist, Inc. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Friedman, Jim and Shel Silverstein
      - In the hills of Shiloh. New York: Hollis Music, Inc., 1963. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Friedman, Leo and Beth Slater Whitson
      - Let me call you sweetheart. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1937., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/4)
      - Meet me tonight in dreamland. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1936., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Friedman, Max and Lew Brown
      - I wish I had died in my cradle. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1926., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Friend, Cliff and Charlie Tobias
      - Time waits for no one. New York: Remick Music Corp., 1944. (Box-folder 507/3)
      - Trade winds. New York: Harms, Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Friend, Cliff, Charlie Tobias and Boyd Bunch
      - The broken record. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1935. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Friml, Rudolf and Brian Hooker
      - Some day. New York: Famous Music Corp., 1925. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Friml, Rudolf, Herbert Stothart, Bob Wright and Chet Forrest
      - The donkey serenade. G. Schirmer, Inc., 1937. (Box-folder 507/3)
    - Friml, Rudolph, Oscar Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein
      - Indian love call. New York: Harms Inc., 1924. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Frisch, Al and Buddy Kaye
      - This is no laughing matter. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1941. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Frisch, Al and Sid Wayne
      - Two different worlds. New York: Princess Music Pub., Corp., 1956. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Fucik, Julius
      - Thunder and blazes. New York: Carl Fischer, 1903. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Fuller, Dean and Marshall Barer
      - Scratch my back. New York: Second Music Pub. Co., Inc., 1956. (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Fyffe, Will
      - I belong to Glasgow. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1921., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/4)
    - Gade, Jacob and Vera Bloom
      - Jalousie. Paris: Edition Charles Brull, 1926. (Box-folder 507/4)
    - Gaillard, Slim and Lee Ricks
      - Cement mixture. New York: American Academy Of Music, 1946. (Box-folder 507/4)
    - Galan, Pacho
      - Ay! cosita linda. New York: Peer International Corp., 1956. (Box-folder 507/4)
    - Galdieri, M. and Don Raye
      - Traveling down a lonely road. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1954. (Box-folder 434/5)
    - Gallop, Sammy and Milton Delugg
      - My lady loves to dance. New York: United Music Corp., 1952. (Box-folder 507/4)
    - Gannon, Kim
      - Croce di oro. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1955., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/5)
    - Garland, Joe
      - In the mood (song). New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1939., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/5)
    - Garner, Erroll and Johnny Burke
      - Misty. New York: Vernon Music Corp., 1954. (Box-folder 434/5)
    - Garrity, Freddie and Mitch Murray
      - I'm telling you now. New York: Miller Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 434/5, 507/4)
    - Garson, Mort and Earl Shuman
      - Left right out of your heart. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1958., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/5)
    - Gaunt, P. and C.H. Hoyt
      - The bowery (Box-folder 507/4)
    - George, Don R.
      - Give. New York: Tobey Music Corp., 1955. (Box-folder 507/4)
    - Gershwin, George and Irving Caesar
      - Swanee. New York: New World Music Corp., 1919. (Box-folder 434/5)
    - Gershwin, George, B.G. DeSylva and Ira Gershwin
      - (I'll build a) Stairway to paradise. New York: New World Music Corp., 1922. (Box-folder 507/4)
    - Gershwin, George and Ira Gerswhin
      - The babbitt and the bromide. New York: New World Music Corp., 1927., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/5)
      - Bidin' my time. New York: New World Music Corp., 1930. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - By Strauss. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1936. (Box-folder 434/5)
      - Clap yo' hands. New York: New World Music Corp., 1926. (Box-folder 434/5)
      - Could you use me. New York: New World Music Corp., 1930., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/5)
      - Do it again. New York: New World Music Corp., 1922. (Box-folder 434/5)
      - Do-do-do. New York: Harms Inc., 1926. (Box-folder 434/5)
      - Embraceable you. New York: New World Music Corp., 1930. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - Fascinating rhythm. New York: New World Music Corp., 1924., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/5)
      - Funny face. New York: New World Music Corp., 1927. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - I got rhythm. New York: New World Music Corp., 1930. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - I love to rhyme. New York: Gershwin Pub. Co., 1938. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - I've got a crush on you. New York: New World Music Corp., 1930. (Box-folder 434/6)
      - Isn't it a pity?. New York: New World Music Corp., 1932. (Box-folder 434/6)
      - It ain't necessarily so. New York: Gershwin Pub. Co., 1935. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - Let's call the whole thing off. New York: Gershwin Pub. Co., 1937. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - Little jazz bird. New York: New World Music Corp., 1924. (Box-folder 434/6)
      - Liza. New York: New World Music Corp., 1929., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/6)
      - Looking for a boy. New York: New World Music Corp., 1925. (Box-folder 434/6)
      - Love walked in. New York: Gershwin Pub. Co., 1938. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - Mine. New York: New World Music Corp., 1933. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - Shall we dance. New York: Gershwin Pub. Co., 1937. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - Slap that bass. New York: Gershwin Pub. Co., 1937. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - Someone to watch over me. New York: Harms, Inc., 1926. (Box-folder 507/4)
      - Strike up the band. New York: New World Music Corp., 1940., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/6)
      - They all laughed. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1937. (Box-folder 434/6)
      - Treat me rough. New York: New World Music Corp., 1944., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/6)
    - Gershwin, George, Ira Gershwin and Dubose Heyward
      - I got plenty o' nuttin'. New York: Gershwin Pub. Co., 1935. (Box-folder 507/4)
    - Gershwin, George and DuBose Heyward
      - Summertime. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1935. (Box-folder 434/5)
    - Gershwin, George, Ballard MacDonald and B.G. DeSylva
      - Somebody loves me. New York: New World Music Corp., 1934. (Box-folder 434/5)
    - Gershwin, Henry, Ann Shepard, Gene Bogard and Tex McCrae
      - It's fat (and it's gonna stay where it's at). New York: Modern Music Masters Pub. Co., 1964. (Box-folder 434/6)
    - Giacomazzi, A.
      - Doctor swing. Milano: Accordo, 1958. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - Sputnik. Milano: Edizioni Curci, 1957. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Giacomazzi, A. and Ardo
      - Bemaciaca. Milano: Accordo, 1959. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Giacomazzi, A. and G.C. Testoni
      - Bonjour, mademoiselle!. Milani: Accordo, 1957. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gibbs, A. Harrington, Joe Grey and Leo Wood
      - Runnin' wild. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1922. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gibson, Arbie and Curt Massey
      - Blues don't mean a thing. New York: Peer International Corp., 1943. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gibson, Don
      - I can't stop loving you. Nashville: Acuff-Rose Pub., Inc., 1958. (Box-folder 434/6)
    - Giefer, George L.
      - Who threw the overalls in Mistress Murphy's chowder? (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gilbert, L. Wolfe and Anatol Friedland
      - Lily of the valley. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1917. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gilbert, Ray and Dorival Caymmi
      - ...And roses and roses. Ipanema Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 434/6)
    - Gilberto, Joao
      - Bim-bom. New York: MCA Music, 1962. (Box-folder 434/6)
      - Ho-ba-la-la. New York: MCA Music, 1962. (Box-folder 434/6)
    - Gilkyson, Terry
      - Walk on, little boy. Hollywood: Montclare Music Corp., 1965. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gill, Rusty and Walt Wesley
      - Too late to be sorry. Chicago: M.M. Cole Pub. Co., 1941. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gillespie, Haven, Seymour Simons and Richard A. Whiting
      - Breezin' along with the breeze. New York: Jerome H. Remick & Co., 1926. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Girard, Adele and Joe Marsala
      - Little sir echo. New York: J.S. Fearis & Bros, 1917. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Giraud, Hubert and Kim Gannon
      - Under Paris skies. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1951. (Box-folder 434/6)
    - Giraud, Hubert and Carl Sigman
      - Willingly. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1958., 2 copies (Box-folder 434/6)
    - Glazer, Tom and Charles Grean
      - The musicians. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1951., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Glenville, Shaun, Frank Miller and Cy Coben
      - Come into the parlor. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1919., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Glogau, Jack and George Graff Jr.
      - Wake up, America!. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1916. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Glover-Kind and Lewis Ilda
      - I do like to be beside the seaside. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1909. (Box-folder 435/1, 507/5)
    - Goetschius, Marjorie and Edna Osser
      - C'n I canoe you up the river. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1949., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Gold, Ernest and Pat Boone
      - The exodus song. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1960. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Goldsmith, Jerry
      - Theme from lilies of the field. New York: Unart Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Goldstein, Bob
      - Washington square. New York: Rayven Music Co., 1963. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Goodman, Benny, Andy Razaf, Chick Webb, and Edgar Sampson
      - Stompin' at the savoy. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1936. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Goodman, Benny, Edgar Sampson, Mitchell Parish
      - Don't be that way. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1938. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gordon, Irving
      - Be anything. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1952., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Mister and Mississippi. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1951., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Two brothers. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1951., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Unforgettable. New York: Bourne, Inc., 1951., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Gordon, Mack and Harry Revel
      - Afraid to dream. New York: Miller Music Inc., 1937. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - From the top of your head. New York: Crawford Music Corp., 1935. (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Goodnight my love. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1936. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - I feel like a feather in the breeze. New York: Famous Music Corp., 1935. (Box-folder 435/1)
      - It's swell of you. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1937. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - Meet the beat of my heart. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - Never in a million years. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1937. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - Paris in the spring. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1935. (Box-folder 435/1)
      - A star fell out of heaven. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1936. (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Stay sweet as you are. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Straight from the shoulder. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Sweet as a song. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1937. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - Swing is here to sway. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1937. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - Take a number from one to ten. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Thanks for ev'rything. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1938. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - There's a lull in my life. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1937. (Box-folder 435/1, 507/5)
      - Wake up and live. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1937. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - When I'm with you. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1936. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - Where in the world. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 507/5)
      - With my eyes wide open I'm dreaming. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 435/1)
      - Without a word of warning. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1935. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Gordon, Mack, Harry Revel and Sidney Clare
      - It was a night in June. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1935. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Gorney, Jay and E.Y. Harburg
      - Brother, can you spare a dime?. New York: Harms, Inc., 1932. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gosh, Bobby
      - We get too soon old. New York: Bobby Gosh, 1965. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Gould, Morton and Dorothy Fields
      - There must be somethin' better than love. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Gould, Morton and Gladys Shelley
      - Pavanne. New York: Mills Music Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Grainger, Porter and Everett Robbins
      - 'Tain't nobody's biz-ness if I do. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1922., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Gray, Jerry and Carl Sigman
      - Pennsylvania 6-5000. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1940. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Greco, Buddy and Ella Fitzgerald
      - Happy time. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Green, Bud, Lew Brown and Ben Homer
      - Sentimental journey. New York: Edwin Morris & Co., 1944. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Green, Bud, Herman Ruby and Sam H. Stept
      - I'll always be in love with you. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1929., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Green, Bud and Sam H. Stept
      - That's my weakness now. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1928., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Green, Eddie
      - A good man is hard to find. New York: Mayfair Music Corp., 1917. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Green, Harold, Mickey Stoner and Martin Block
      - I guess I'll have to dream the rest. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1941. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Green, Joe and Jeanne Gravelle
      - Dawn of to-morrow. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1954., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Greene, Mort, Mann Curtis and Jerome Gottler
      - He took her for a sleighride (in the good old summertime). New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1941. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Greenidge, John
      - For you and me and Uncle Sam. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Greer, Jesse and Raymond Klages
      - Just you, just me. New York: Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Corp., 1929., 2 copies (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Gross, Walter and Jack Lawrence
      - Tenderly. New York: Edwin H. Morris & Co., Inc., 1946. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Gruber, Edmund L.
      - The caissons go rolling by. New York: Philip Egner and Frederick C. Mayer, 1921. (Box-folder 507/5)
    - Grudeff, Marian and Raymond Jessel
      - A married man. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1964. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Guion, David W.
      - Home on the range. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1930. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Guizar, Pepe
      - Guadalajara. New York: Peer International Corp., 1937. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Guthrie, Jack and Woody Guthrie
      - Oklahoma hills. New York: Michael H. Goldsen, Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Hadjidakis, M. and Arthur Altman
      - All alone am I. New York: Duchess Music Corp., 1959. (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hadley, Henry and Guy Wood
      - October twilight. New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., 1922., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hager, Earle and Dick Rogers
      - Harlem nocturne. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1940., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hagg, Gustav
      - O vermeland, thou lovely. G. Schirmer, Inc., 1909. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Haggart, Bob and Johnny Burke
      - What's new?. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1934. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Hairston, Jester
      - Angels rolled de stone away. New York: Bourne, Co., 1949. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - Dis train. Hollywood: Schumann Music Co., 1954. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - God's gonna buil' up Zion's wall. New York: Bourne Co., 1960. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - Hand me down. Hollywood: Schumann Music Co., 1951. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - I can tell the world. New York: Bourne Co., 1959. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - In dat great gittin' up mornin'. Hollywood: Schumann Music Co., 1952. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - Joshua fit de battle of Jericho. Hollywood: Schumann Music Co., 1952. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Hale, Travis, Dean Fitzer and Prescott Brown
      - Oh bury me out on the prairie (The cowboy's lament). San Francisco: Villa Moret, Inc., 1927. (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hall, Wendall
      - I don't mind the rain. Chicago: Wendall Hall Music Maker Productions, 1953., 2 copies (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Hall, Wendell Woods
      - Funny little dixie tune. Chicago: Forster Music Pub., Inc., 1965. (Box-folder 435/2)
      - I don't know why I love you. Chicago: Forster Music Pub., Inc., 1920., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hamblen, Stuart
      - Open up your heart (and let the sun shine in). Arcadia: Hamblen Music Co., 1953. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Hamilton, Arthur
      - He needs me. New York: Criterion Music Corp., 1955. (Box-folder 435/2)
      - Rain sometimes. New York: Edwin H. Morris & Co., Inc., 1965. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - Sing a rainbow. New York: Criterion Music Corp., 1955. (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hamlisch, Marvin and Howard Liebling
      - Sunshine, lollipops and rainbows. Miami: Chas. H. Hansen Music Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Hampton, Lionel and Curley Hamner
      - Hey! ba-ba-re-bop. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1945. (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Handy, W.C.
      - Friendless blues. Handy Bros. Music Co., Inc., 1926. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - Saint Louis blues. New York: Handy Bros Music Co., Inc., 1914. (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Handy, W.C. and George A. Norton
      - The Memphis blues. New York: Theron C. Bennett, 1913. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Hanley, James F. and Grant Clarke
      - Second hand rose. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1921., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hanley, James F. and Ballard MacDonald
      - Indiana. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1919., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
      - Rose of Washington Square. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1919., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
      - Somebody else-not me. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1920., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hanley, James F., Ballard MacDonald and Joe Goodwin
      - Breeze (blow my baby back to me). New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1919., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Harlene, Leigh and Ned Washington
      - Pinocchio (souvenir album). New York: Bourne, Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 435/2)
      - I've got no strings. New York: Irving Berlin, Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Harmati, Sandor and Edward Heyman
      - Blue bird of happiness. New York: T.B. Harms Co., 1934. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Harrell, Kelly
      - Away out on the mountain. New York: Peer International Corp., 1928. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Harris, Charles K.
      - After the ball. Ashley Pub. Inc., 1962. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - And a little child shall lead them. New York: Chas. K. Music Pub. Co., Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 507/6)
      - Break the news to mother. New York: Chas. K. Music Pub. Co., Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 507/6)
    - Harris, Lewis and John Jacob Loeb
      - The maharajah of Magador. New York: Mutual Music Society, Inc., 1947. (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hatch, Tony
      - Call me. New York: Duchess Music Corp., 1965., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
      - Downtown. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1964. (Box-folder 435/2)
      - I know a place. New York: Duchess Music Corp., 1965., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
      - My love. New York: Duchess Music Corp., 1965., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Hatch, Tony and Jackie Trent
      - Color my world. New York: Northern Music Corp., 1966. (Box-folder 435/2)
      - I couldn't live without your love. New York: Northern Music Corp., 1966. (Box-folder 435/2)
      - Who am I. New York: Duchess Music Corp., 1966., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Haufrecht, Herbert, edited by
      - Folk sing: a handbook for pickers and singers. New York: Hollis Music, Inc. (Box-folder 507/7)
    - Havelka, Charles F.
      - How you stroke Santa's whiskers. St. Louis: Shattinger, 1952., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/3)
      - The politician polka. St. Louis: Shattinger, 1952., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/3)
      - What the sun does for a rainbow a smile will do for you. St. Louis: Shattinger, 1952., 2 copies (Box-folder 435/3)
    - Hayman, Richard, Lee Daniels and S. Parker
      - Dansero. Chicago: B & F Music Co., Inc., 1953. (Box-folder 435/3)
    - Haymes, Bob and Alan Brandt
      - That's all. Los Angeles: Travis Music Co., 1952. (Box-folder 507/7)
    - Haymes, Bob and Marty Clarke